Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Records 5685
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VII: Papers & Correspondence of Local Unions
  - Sub-Series Local 64, 1958-1969
    - Membership Acceptance Initiation Fee Letter, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 17-19)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-F, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 20-24)
    - Shop Correspondence, G-I, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 25)
    - Shop Correspondence, J-L, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 26)
    - Shop Correspondence, M-O, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 27)
    - Princess Ribbon Corp. Strike, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 28)
    - Shop Correspondence, P-R, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 29)
    - Shop Correspondence, S-T, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 30-31)
    - Shop Correspondence, U-W, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 32)
    - Shop Correspondence, X-Z, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 33)
    - Shop Correspondence, J.F. Zucker Co., 1963 (Box 77, Folder 34)
    - Worker Correspondence, A-L, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 35)
    - Worker Correspondence, M-Z, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 36)
    - Auction House Negotiations, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 37)
    - Contract Terminations, A-L, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 38)
    - Contract Terminations, M-Z, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 39)
    - Form Letters, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 40)
    - Fur Merchants Employers, Council, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 41)
    - Membership Notification, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 42-45)
    - Minutes, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 46-47)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-C, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Shop Correspondence, D-F, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Furriers Supply Merchant Association, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Shop Correspondence, G-I, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Shop Correspondence, J-L, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Shop Correspondence, M-O, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Shop Correspondence, NY Auction House, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Shop Correspondence, NY Fur Cleaners Assoc., 1964 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Shop Correspondence, P-R, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Shop Correspondence, S-T, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Shop Correspondence, U-W, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Shop Correspondence, X-Z, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Worker Correspondence, A-L, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Worker Correspondence, M-Z, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Contract Terms, A-L, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Contract Terms, M-Z, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Form Letters, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 17-19)
    - Freedman & Sons Corp., NLRB, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - Initiation Fee Letters, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 21-25)
    - Minutes, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 26-27)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-C, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 28)
    - Shop Correspondence, D-F, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 29)
    - Shop Correspondence, Fur Cuttings Dealer Assn., 1965 (Box 78, Folder 30)
    - Shop Correspondence, Fur Merchants Employers Council, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 31-32)
    - Shop Correspondence, Furriers Supply Merchants Assn., 1965 (Box 78, Folder 33)
    - Shop Correspondence, G-I, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 34)
    - Shop Correspondence, Hudson's Bay Co., 1965 (Box 78, Folder 35)
    - Shop Correspondence, J-L, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 36)
    - Shop Correspondence, M-O, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 37)
    - Shop Correspondence, Mary's Monograms Arbitration, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 38)
    - Shop Correspondence, NY Auction House, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 39)
    - Shop Correspondence, NY Fur Cleaners Assoc., 1965 (Box 78, Folder 40)
    - Shop Correspondence, NY Monogram Association, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 41)
    - Shop Correspondence, P-R, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 42)
    - Shop Correspondence, S-T, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 43)
    - Shop Correspondence, Textile Association of the Fur Industry, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 44)
    - Shop Correspondence, U-W, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 45)
    - Shop Correspondence, X-Z, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 46)
    - Worker Correspondence, A-L, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 47-48)
    - Worker Correspondence, M-Z, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 49-50)
    - Form Letters, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 51-53)
    - Membership Letter to Employees, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 54)
    - Minutes - Executive Board, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 55)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 56)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-B, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Association Fur Man, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Auction Negotiations, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Shop Correspondence, C-D, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Shop Correspondence, E-F, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Fur Cutting Dealers' Association of NY, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Fur Merchants Employers, Council, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Fur Merchants Employers, Council, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Shop Correspondence, G-H, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Shop Correspondence, I-J, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Shop Correspondence, K-L, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Shop Correspondence, Linen Embroidery, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Shop Correspondence, M-N, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Shop Correspondence, NY Auction House, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Shop Correspondence, Fur Cleaners Assn., 1966 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Shop Correspondence, NY Monogram Association, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Shop Correspondence, O-P, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Shop Correspondence, Q-R, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Shop Correspondence, S, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Shop Correspondence, T-U, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Shop Correspondence, Textile Assn., 1966 (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - Shop Correspondence, V-W, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - Shop Correspondence, X-Z, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Worker Correspondence, A-L, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - Worker Correspondence, M-Z, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - Form Letters, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - Minutes, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 26B)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-B, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 27)
    - Shop Correspondence, Associated Fur Manufacturers, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 28)
    - Shop Correspondence, C-D, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - Shop Correspondence, E-F, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - Shop Correspondence, Free Lance Assorters, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 31)
    - Shop Correspondence, Fur Cuttings Dealer Assn., 1968 (Box 79, Folder 32)
    - Shop Correspondence, Fur Merchants Employers Council, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 33)
    - Shop Correspondence, Furriers Supply Merchants Assn., 1968 (Box 79, Folder 34)
    - Shop Correspondence, G-H, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 35)
    - Shop Correspondence, Hudson's Bay Co., 1968 (Box 79, Folder 36)
    - Shop Correspondence, I-J, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 37)
    - Shop Correspondence, K-L, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 38)
    - Shop Correspondence, M-N, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 39)
    - Shop Correspondence, NY Auction House, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 40)
    - Shop Correspondence, NY Fur Cleaners Assoc., 1968 (Box 79, Folder 41)
    - Shop Correspondence, O-P, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 42)
    - Shop Correspondence, Q-R, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 43)
    - Shop Correspondence, S, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 44)
    - Shop Correspondence, T-U, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 45)
    - Shop Correspondence, Textile Association of the Fur Industry, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 46)
    - Shop Correspondence, United Fur Manufacturers, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 47)
    - Shop Correspondence, V-W, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 48)
    - Shop Correspondence, X-Z, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 49)
    - Worker Correspondence, A-Z, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 50)
    - Form Letters, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 51-52)
    - Minutes, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 53)
    - Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 54)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-B, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 55)
    - Shop Correspondence, Associated Fur Manufacturers, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 56)
    - Shop Correspondence, C-D, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 57)
    - Shop Correspondence, E-F, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 58)
    - Shop Correspondence, Free Lance Assorters, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 59)
    - Shop Correspondence, Fur Cuttings Dealer Assn., 1969 (Box 79, Folder 60)
    - Shop Correspondence, Fur Merchants Employers Council, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 61)
    - Shop Correspondence, Furriers Supply Merchants Assn., 1969 (Box 79, Folder 62)
    - Shop Correspondence, G-H, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 63)
    - Shop Correspondence, Hudson's Bay Co., 1969 (Box 79, Folder 64)
    - Shop Correspondence, I-J, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 65)
    - Shop Correspondence, K-L, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 66)
    - Shop Correspondence, M-N, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 67)
    - Shop Correspondence, NY Auction House, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 68)
    - Shop Correspondence, NY Fur Cleaners Assoc., 1969 (Box 79, Folder 69)
    - Shop Correspondence, NY Monogram Association, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Shop Correspondence, O-P, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Shop Correspondence, Q-R, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Shop Correspondence, S, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Shop Correspondence, T-U, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Shop Correspondence, Textile Association of the Fur Industry, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Shop Correspondence, V-W, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Shop Correspondence, X-Z, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Worker Correspondence, A-Z, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series Local 88, 1962-1969
    - April - Elections Committee, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 10-14)
    - January - Organizers Reports, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 15-16)
    - February - Organizers Reports, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 17-18)
    - March - Organizers Reports, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 19-20)
    - April - Organizers Reports, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 21-22)
    - May - Organizers Reports, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 23-24)
    - June - Organizers Reports, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 25-26)
    - July - Organizers Reports, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 27-28)
    - August - Organizers Reports, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 29-30)
    - September - Organizers Reports, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 31-32)
    - October - Organizers Reports, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 33-34)
    - November - Organizers Reports, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 35-36)
    - December - Organizers Reports, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 37-38)
    - Contract Termination Notices to Boards, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 39)
    - Form Letters, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 40-41)
    - Minutes, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 42)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-C, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 43)
    - Shop Correspondence, D-F, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 44)
    - Shop Correspondence, G-I, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 45)
    - Shop Correspondence, J-L, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 46)
    - Shop Correspondence, M-O, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 47)
    - Shop Correspondence, P-R, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 48)
    - Shop Correspondence, S-T, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 49)
    - Shop Correspondence, U-W, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 50)
    - Shop Correspondence, United Fur Cutters, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 51-53)
    - Worker Correspondence, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 54)
    - Contract Termination, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 55)
    - Election Committee, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 56-59)
    - Form Letters, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Vacation Pay Claims, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-C, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Shop Correspondence, American Photocopy Equipment Co. - Contract Negotiations, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 5-9)
    - Shop Correspondence, D-F, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Shop Correspondence, G-I, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Shop Correspondence, J-L, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Shop Correspondence, M-O, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Shop Correspondence, P-R, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Shop Correspondence, S-T, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Shop Correspondence, U-W, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Shop Correspondence, X-Z, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Worker Correspondence, A-L, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Worker Correspondence, M-Z, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Contract Termination, A-L, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Contract Termination, M-Z, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Form Letters, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 22-23)
    - Minutes, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 24-25)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-C, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Shop Correspondence, Crown-Monarch of Shop Chairman, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - Shop Correspondence, D-F, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - Shop Correspondence, Fur Blender Guild, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - Shop Correspondence, G-I, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 30)
    - Shop Correspondence, J-L, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 31)
    - Shop Correspondence, M-O, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 32)
    - Shop Correspondence, P-R, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 33)
    - Shop Correspondence, S-T, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 34)
    - Shop Correspondence, Trousseau Monogram, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 35)
    - Shop Correspondence, U-Z, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 36)
    - Worker Correspondence, A-L, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 37)
    - Worker Correspondence, M-Z, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 38)
    - Form Letters, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 39-40)
    - Minutes, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 40-41)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-B, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 42)
    - Shop Correspondence, C-D, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 43)
    - Shop Correspondence, E-F, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 44)
    - Shop Correspondence, Fur Blender Guild, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 45)
    - Shop Correspondence, Fur Processors Association, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 46)
    - Shop Correspondence, G-H, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 47)
    - Shop Correspondence, I-J, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 48)
    - Shop Correspondence, K-L, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 49)
    - Shop Correspondence, William Kopolsky, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 50)
    - Shop Correspondence, M-N, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 51)
    - Shop Correspondence, O-P, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 52)
    - Shop Correspondence, Q-R, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 53)
    - Shop Correspondence, R&J Tanning, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 54-56)
    - Shop Correspondence, Rabbit Dressers Institute, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 57)
    - Shop Correspondence, S, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 58)
    - Shop Correspondence, T-U, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 59)
    - Shop Correspondence, V-W, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 60)
    - Worker Correspondence, A-Z, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 61)
    - Form Letters, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 62)
    - Minutes, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 63)
    - Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 64)
    - Overtime Claims, Crown Monarch, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 65-66)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-B, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 67)
    - Shop Correspondence, Brooklyn Better Bleach Arb., 1967 (Box 81, Folder 68)
    - Shop Correspondence, C-D, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 69)
    - Shop Correspondence, E-F, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 70)
    - Shop Correspondence, Fur Blender Guild, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 71)
    - Shop Correspondence, Fur Processors Association, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 72)
    - Shop Correspondence, G-H, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Shop Correspondence, I-J, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Shop Correspondence, K-L, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Shop Correspondence, M-N, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Shop Correspondence, O-P, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Shop Correspondence, Q-R, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Shop Correspondence, Rabbit Dressers Institute, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Shop Correspondence, S, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Shop Correspondence, T-U, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Shop Correspondence, W-Z, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Worker Correspondence, A-Z, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Form Letters, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Minutes, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-B, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Shop Correspondence, C-D, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - Shop Correspondence, E-F, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - Shop Correspondence, Fur Blender Guild, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - Shop Correspondence, Fur Processors Association, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - Shop Correspondence, K-S, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - Shop Correspondence, T-Z, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 21)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-Z, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series Local 150, 1962-1969
    - Elections Committee, 1962 (Box 82, Folder 23-25)
    - Apprentice Training Program, 1962 (Box 82, Folder 26)
    - Contract Termination Notices, 1962 (Box 82, Folder 27-31)
    - Form Letters, 1962 (Box 82, Folder 32-33)
    - Minutes, 1962 (Box 82, Folder 34)
    - January/February, Organization Reports, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 35)
    - March-November, Organization Reports, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 36-44)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-C, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 45-47)
    - Shop Correspondence, American Photography Equipment Co. - NLRB Election, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 48)
    - Shop Correspondence, D-F, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 49)
    - Shop Correspondence, Filtors, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 50)
    - Shop Correspondence, G-I, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 51)
    - Shop Correspondence, J-L, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 52)
    - Shop Correspondence, Joseph A. Kaplan & Sons, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 53)
    - Shop Correspondence, M-O, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 54)
    - Shop Correspondence, Metal Parts Processing, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 55)
    - Shop Correspondence, Mutual Sewing Machine, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 56)
    - Shop Correspondence, P-R, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 57)
    - Shop Correspondence, Plant Manufacturing - NLRB election; legal material; post election, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 58-61)
    - Shop Correspondence, Radel Leather, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 62)
    - Shop Correspondence, S-T, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 63)
    - Shop Correspondence, Singer Sewing Machine, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 64)
    - Shop Correspondence, Tangel Material Handling Equip., 1963 (Box 82, Folder 65)
    - Shop Correspondence, U-W, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 66)
    - Worker Correspondence, A-Z, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 67)
    - Contract Termination, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 1-4)
    - Elections Committee, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 5-9)
    - Form Letters, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 10-12)
    - Minutes, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 13-14)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-C, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 15-16)
    - Shop Correspondence, American Photography Equipment Co. - strike; welfare plans, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 17-23)
    - Shop Correspondence, D-F, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 24)
    - Shop Correspondence, G-I, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 25)
    - Shop Correspondence, Industrial Electrical Contractors, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 26)
    - Shop Correspondence, J-L, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 27)
    - Shop Correspondence, M-O, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 28)
    - Shop Correspondence, Mutual Sewing Machine, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 29)
    - Shop Correspondence, P-R, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 30)
    - Shop Correspondence, Planet Manufacturing Corp. - NLRB election; leaflets, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 31-33)
    - Shop Correspondence, Ramer Industrial Inc., 1964 (Box 83, Folder 34)
    - Shop Correspondence, S-T, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 35-36)
    - Shop Correspondence, Sculpture House - NLRB election, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 37)
    - Shop Correspondence, Singer Sewing Machine, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 38)
    - Shop Correspondence, Tangel Manufacturing Handling, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 39)
    - Shop Correspondence, U-W, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 40-41)
    - Shop Correspondence, United Mineral & Chemical Corp. - Adolf Thomas claim; injunction processes - NLRB cases; unemployment insurance, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 42-44)
    - Shop Correspondence, X-Z, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 45)
    - Worker Correspondence, A-Z, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 46-47)
    - Contract Termination, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 1-4)
    - Form Letters, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 5-7)
    - Minutes, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-C, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Shop Correspondence, APECO - Walter Wall; decertification, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 10-11)
    - Shop Correspondence, C&W Sewing Machine - NLRB Certification, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Shop Correspondence, Celebrity, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Shop Correspondence, Cooper Electric Water Cooler, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Shop Correspondence, D-F, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Shop Correspondence, Dyno Merchandise Corp., 1965 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - Shop Correspondence, Five Star Hardware, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 17-18)
    - Shop Correspondence, G-I, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - Shop Correspondence, Industrial Electrical Contractors, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - Shop Correspondence, J-L, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - Shop Correspondence, M-O, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Shop Correspondence, Mutual Sewing Machine, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - Shop Correspondence, Nettie Electric Arbitration, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 24)
    - Shop Correspondence, P-R, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 25)
    - Shop Correspondence, S-T, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 26-29)
    - Shop Correspondence, Stacey Hardware, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 30)
    - Shop Correspondence, Steel Partition, Shelving, & Rack, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 31)
    - Shop Correspondence, United Mechanics, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 32-34)
    - Shop Correspondence, United Mineral, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 35-38)
    - Shop Correspondence, Unity Sewing Supply, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 39)
    - Shop Correspondence, Weinstein, Joseph, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 40-41)
    - Worker Correspondence, A-Z, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 42)
    - Form Letters, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 43-44)
    - Minutes, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 45)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-B, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 2-3)
    - Shop Correspondence, Busy Jack Shop Co., 1966 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Shop Correspondence, C-D, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 5-6)
    - Shop Correspondence, Delta Cleaners, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Shop Correspondence, E-F, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Shop Correspondence, Fur Machine Dealers, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Shop Correspondence, G-H, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Shop Correspondence, Helvetia Sewing, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Shop Correspondence, I-J, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Shop Correspondence, K-L, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 13-14)
    - Shop Correspondence, Kenston Corp., 1966 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Shop Correspondence, M-N, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Shop Correspondence, Mutual Sewing Machine, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 17-19)
    - Shop Correspondence. O-P, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Shop Correspondence, Q-R, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Shop Correspondence, Railey, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 22-24)
    - Shop Correspondence, S, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 25)
    - Shop Correspondence, Stanley, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 26)
    - Shop Correspondence, Partition Shelving & Rack, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 27)
    - Shop Correspondence, Style Undies, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 28)
    - Shop Correspondence, T-U, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 29)
    - Shop Correspondence, United Mechanics Misc., 1966 (Box 85, Folder 30-31)
    - Shop Correspondence, V-W, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 32)
    - Shop Correspondence, Weinstein, Joseph, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 33)
    - Shop Correspondence, Westpfal's Electric, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 34)
    - Shop Correspondence, X-Z, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 35)
    - Worker Correspondence, A-L, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 36)
    - Worker Correspondence, M-Z, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 37)
    - Apprentice Training Program, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 38-39)
    - Form Letters, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 40)
    - Minutes, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 41)
    - Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 42)
    - Shop Correspondence, A-B, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 43)
    - Shop Correspondence, C-D, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 44)
    - Shop Correspondence, E-F, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 45)
    - Shop Correspondence, G-H, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 46)
    - Shop Correspondence, I-J, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 47)
    - Shop Correspondence, Industrial Electrical Contractors, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 48)
    - Shop Correspondence, Industrial Steel Equipment, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 49)
    - Shop Correspondence, K-L, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 50)
    - Shop Correspondence, M-N, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 51)
    - Shop Correspondence, Milton Opal, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 52)
    - Shop Correspondence, Mutual Sewing Machine, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 53-54)
    - Shop Correspondence, O-P, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 55)
    - Shop Correspondence, Q-R, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 56-57)
    - Shop Correspondence, Romero Metal, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 58)
    - Shop Correspondence, Stanley, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 59-60)
    - Shop Correspondence, Steel Partition, Shelving, & Rack, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Shop Correspondence, T-U, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 2)